equestriadaily.com 2019-12-12

# Equestria Daily - MLP Stuff!: EQD Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Equestria Daily collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [https://www.equestriadaily.com](https://www.equestriadaily.com/) website, the Equestria Daily Forums at https://forums.equestriadaily.com and the mobile Equestria Daily Android and iOS app (from here on out all referred to as "Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Equestria Daily.

Web browser cookies  
Our site and third-party tools may use "cookies" to enhance user experience. All first party cookies are stored for session retention purposes only and contain no personal or tracking information.  User s may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

Blogger/Google Analytics  
The Blogger engine may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and web browser used. This information is used only for functional purposes.

When the user visits the site for the first time, a notification from Blogger will appear at the top informing the user about the non personal and personal data Blogger and Google Analytics collect (if applicable). 

The full Google privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

Disqus

The third-party Disqus comment system created by Disqus Inc. uses cookies to maintain user sessions. This privacy policy does not cover the use of information and cookies set by Disqus Inc. plugins. The Disqus Inc. Privacy Policy can be found [here](https://help.disqus.com/customer/en/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy).

 **Third-party advertisements on the website**

Some of the advertisements you see on EquestriaDaily.com are delivered by third parties who also collect information through their own cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies about your online activities, either on our services or across the Internet, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties include advertisers, advertising agencies, and ad networks that may collect information about you when you view or interact with one of their advertisements and may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites.

Third parties may serve, track and/or analyze ads on our services, and thereby may collect information about your online activities. EquestriaDaily.com does not have access to the information these third parties may collect about your interests to deliver relevant advertising to you, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

These companies may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes on both browser and mobile app platforms.   
In addition, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"), which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored advertisements from member companies. To opt out of information collection by NAI member companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer opt out page here: 

 **Third-party advertisements on mobile**

The advertisements you see on the Equestria Daily app are delivered by the Google Admob network. The Google Admob network might collect information through their own cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies about your online activities, either on our services or across the Internet, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. 

Admob may serve, track and/or analyze ads in the Equestria Daily app and collect information to deliver more personalized ads. The full Google privacy policy (including AdMob) can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).   
Equestria Daily does not have access to any data, personal or non personal, that the Admob network may collect to deliver relevant advertising to you. 

Users from the EEA will be offered a choice between personalized and non personalized ads at app startup. Choosing non personalized ads will automatically opt-out the user from any collection of personal data by the Admob network. This choice can be changed (and consent for data collection thereby granted or revoked) in the Options screen of the app.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Changes to this privacy policy

Equestria Daily has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send out a notification on social media. In case of major changed a blog post will also be published informing users of the update. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are handling the personal information we collect.

Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Equestria Daily  

This document was last updated on May 31, 2018
